RG 005:036, Office of the Governor: Ella Grasso (1975-1980)
Connecticut State Library
- Part IV Subject Files, 1971-1982
  - Transportation - DOT (Box 647)
    - [Aviation Miscellaneous] (B), 1980-1981 (Box 647)
    - [Bradley Airport] (B), 1980 (Box 647)
    - Bradley International Airport Authority, 1977 (Box 647)
    - Bradley - Name Change (B), 1981 (Box 647)
    - [Bus Service] (B), 1980-1981 (Box 647)
    - Buttonball Bridge (B), 1980 (Box 647)
    - Conn. Company - Buses, 1973-1975 (Box 647)
    - Connecticut Transit, 1979 (Box 647)
    - [Conrail/Amtrak] (Box 647)
    - Control Plan, 1976-1978 (Box 648)
    - [Governor’s Railroad Advisory Task Force], 1980-1981 (Box 648)
    - [Letters] (Box 648)
      - A (B), 1980-1981 (Box 648)
      - B (B), 1980-1981 (Box 648)
      - C (B), 1980-1981 (Box 648)
      - D (B), 1980 (Box 648)
      - E,F (B), 1980 (Box 649)
      - G (B), 1979-1980 (Box 649)
      - H-J (B), 1980 (Box 649)
      - K-L (B), 1980-1981 (Box 649)
      - M (B), 1980 (Box 649)
      - N-O (B), 1980 (Box 650)
      - P-R (B), 1980-1981 (Box 650)
      - S (B), 1980 (Box 650)
      - T-U (B), 1980-1981 (Box 650)
      - V-Z (B), 1980-1981 (Box 650)
    - Merritt Parkway, 1973-1980 (Box 650)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1981 (Box 650)
    - [Motor Vehicles] (B), 1980 (Box 650)
    - Niantic River Bridge - Groton - East Lime (B), 1979-1980 (Box 651)
    - Poughkeepsie Bridge, 1979-1980 (Box 651)
    - [Rail - Letters] (Box 651)
      - A-K (B), 1980 (Box 651)
      - L-Z (B), 1980 (Box 651)
    - Rail Users Meetings (O), 1980 August 29 (Box 651)
    - [Ridesharing] (B), 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Ridesharing Reports], 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Route 6,7,9] (B), 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Route I-84] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 652)
    - [Route I-84/Union Carbide], 1978-1979 (Box 652)
    - [Route I-91 and I-95] (B), 1980 (Box 652)
    - Route 364 (B), 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Southwest Conn. Energy Meeting/Van Pooling), 1979 June 27 (Box 652)
    - [State Rail Plan], 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Snow and Ice], 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Toll Plazas] (B), 1980-1981 (Box 652)
    - Town and Assistance Program (B), 1980 (Box 652)
    - [Van Pooling] (Box 652)
  - [Treasurer, Conn. State] (B), 1980-1981 (Box 653)
  - Tributes to ETG (B), 1981 (Box 653)
  - [Tri-State Regional Planning Commission], 1980 (Box 653)
  - [United Way], 1980 (Box 653)
  - [Urban Action Task Force, 1978-1979 (Box 653)
  - [Veterans Administration] (B), 1980 (Box 653)
  - Veterans - Fairfield Site (B), 1980 (Box 653)
  - [Visa] (B), 1980-1982 (Box 653)
  - [Volunteer Activity] (Box 653)
  - [Wadsworth Athenaeum], 1981 (Box 654)
  - [Washington Office], 1980 (Box 654)
  - [Welcome] (O), 1980 (Box 654)
  - White House Conference on Aging (B), 1980 March (Box 654)
  - White House Conference on Families (B), 1980 (Box 654)
  - [White House Conference on Families], 1978 (Box 654)
  - White House Conference on Families - Appointments (O), 1980 (Box 654)
  - [Wildey, William] (B), 1972-1980 (Box 654)
  - [Women - Hartford College], 1980 (Box 654)
  - [Women - Miscellaneous], 1980 (Box 654)
  - [Women - Permanent Commission on Status of Women] (B), 1980-1981 (Box 654)
- Part V Subject Files, 1979-1982
  - Ack (B), 1978-1980 (Box 655)
  - Acknowledgments (B), 1978 (Box 655)
  - [Acknowledgments - condolences], 1981 (Box 655)
  - [Acknowledgments - condolences] (B), 1981 (Box 656)
  - [Acknowledgments - condolences], 1981 April (Box 657)
  - Acknowledgments (Box 657)
    - Donations/Contributions in Memory of Ella Grasso (O), 1981 (Box 658)
    - For Flowers or Special Items for Governor’s Lying-in-State and Funeral (O) (Box 658)
    - For Get Well Letters and Cards (O), 1981 (Box 658)
    - For Mass Cards (O), 1981 (Box 658)
    - For Special Gifts and Cards Sent to Governor Grasso (O), 1981 (Box 658)
    - For Telegrams Sent on Occasion of Death of Ella Grasso (B), 1981 (Box 658)
    - For Telegrams sent on Occasion of Governor’s Passing (B), 1981 (Box 658)
  - [Acknowledgments - Get Well Letters], 1980 (Box 658)
  - [Acknowledgments - Get Well Letters] (O), 1980 (Box 659)
  - [Acknowledgments - Get Well Letters] (B), 1980 (Box 659)
  - [Acknowledgments - Memorial Gifts] (B), 1981 (Box 659)
  - [Acknowledgments - Memorial Gifts] (B), 1981 (Box 660)
  - [Acknowledgments - Misc.] (B), 1981 (Box 660)
  - Acknowledgments - to Participants in Lying-in-State and Funeral (O), 1981 (Box 660)
  - Acknowledgments to Schools/Students for Cards, Messages, (O) (Box 660)
  - Notes, etc., 1981 (Box 660)
  - Administrative Services, 1979 (Box 660)
  - Aetna, 1979 (Box 660)
  - Aging, 1979 (Box 660)
  - Appointments (I), 1978 (Box 660)
  - Appointments for Schedule - Letters Written (B), 1974-1975 (Box 660)
  - Appointments with Governor/Requests for (B), 1979 (Box 660)
  - Articles, 1978 (Box 661)
  - Arts, 1979 (Box 661)
  - Bank Accounts, 1975 (Box 661)
  - Bank Account, 1976 (Box 661)
  - Bankers - New York, 1976 (Box 661)
  - Banking, 1979 (Box 661)
  - Barney House, 1979 March 6 (Box 661)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Thirteen Original States, 1979 (Box 661)
  - [Bond Commission], 1978-1979 (Box 661)
  - Bond Commission, 1975 (Box 662)
  - Books (B), 1978 (Box 662)
  - Books - Thanks, 1975-1976 (Box 662)
  - [Branford House - UCONN], 1979 (Box 662)
  - Budget, 1979 (Box 662)
  - Budget Analisis (O), 1979 (Box 662)
  - Budget Presentation (Box 662)
  - Campaign File, 1978 (Box 662)
  - Campaign, Governor’s, 1978 (Box 662)
  - [Carmelite Sisters Golden Jubilee], 1979 (Box 662)
  - Cecchini (Lebanon Girl Who Died), 1978 (Box 662)
  - Central Connecticut State College, 1979 (Box 662)
  - Checks to General Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 662)
  - [Children and Youth Services] - DC + YS, 1979 (Box 662)
  - China Trip, 1980 (Box 662)
  - China Visit, 1979-1980 (Box 662)
  - City of Hartford, 1978 (Box 662)
  - Christmas Cards (B), 1978-1979 (Box 662)
  - Civil Preparedness, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Clippings, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Commerce, 1978-1979 (Box 663)
  - Commerce Department, 1978 (Box 663)
  - Commerce/Ground Breaking in Marlborough, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Comptroller, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Condolences (B), 1979-1980 (Box 663)
  - Condolences to Grasso (I), 1981 (Box 663)
  - CONEG, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Congrats from ETG (B), 1979 (Box 663)
  - Congrats to Governor (B), 1979 (Box 663)
  - Congressional Record, 1974 (Box 663)
  - Connecticut Conference of Mayors, 1975 (Box 663)
  - Connecticut Farm Bureau Association, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Connecticut State Employees Association (B), 1974-1975 (Box 663)
  - Consumer Advisory Council, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Consumer Protection, 1979 (Box 663)
  - Contributions (B), 1979 (Box 663)
  - Contributions (B), 1974-1975 (Box 663)
  - Contributions (B), 1976 (Box 663)
  - Contributions (B), 1978 (Box 664)
  - Council of Economic Advisors (B), 1978 (Box 664)
  - [Danbury State Fair - Ribbon], 1979 (Box 664)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Democratic Town Committee, etc., 1978 (Box 664)
  - Dinosaur State Park (I), 1979 (Box 664)
  - Discretionary Fund (B), 1978-1979 (Box 664)
  - Distinguished Service Award - Honorable Ella Grasso, 1979 August 6 (Box 664)
  - Donations, Small Gifts, Requests, 1975 (Box 664)
  - Dynamics Unlimited, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Easter Cards (B), 1979 (Box 664)
  - Easter Greetings (B), 1978 (Box 664)
  - Editorial Writers, 1975 (Box 664)
  - Education (Box 664)
  - [Education - CEA Midwinter Meeting], 1979 (Box 664)
  - [Education - Suffolk University School of Law], 1980 (Box 664)
  - Electric Boat, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Employment, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Endorsements, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Energy, 1979 (Box 664)
  - [Environment] - DEP, 1979 (Box 664)
  - Federal Government, 1978 (Box 664)
  - Fenn, Albert File (B), 1978 (Box 664)
  - Finance Advisory Committee - Bond Authorization, 1975 (Box 665)
  - [Finance Advisory Committee] - FAC Procedure, 1975-1977 (Box 665)
  - Flowers - Hospitalization (B), 1980 April (Box 665)
  - Flowers from the Governor (B), 1979 (Box 665)
  - Flowers Sent, 1978 (Box 665)
  - Flowers to Governor (B), 1979 (Box 665)
  - Funeral Clippings, 1981 (Box 665)
  - “Georgie” Keel - Laying Ceremony, 1979 (Box 665)
  - Get Well (B), 1981 (Box 665)
  - Get Well Greetings - Hospitalization (B), 1980 April (Box 665)
  - Get Well Greetings - Hospitalization (B), 1980 April (Box 666)
  - [Get Well Letters] (I), 1980 (Box 666)
  - Get Well - Sympathy (O), 1978 (Box 666)
  - Gifts from Governor (B), 1979 (Box 666)
  - Gifts (B), 1978 (Box 666)
  - Governor’s Birthday (B), 1980 (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Friday Evening Schedule, 1975 May 16 (Box 667)
  - [Governor’s Illness], 1980 (Box 667)
  - [Governor’s] Luncheon, 1827 December (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Party 12/23 - 6:00 Guest List (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Personal Information, 1977-1978 (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Personal Letters (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Personal List of Addresses, 1976-1977 (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Christmas Donations, 1978 (Box 667)
  - Governor’s Christmas List, 1978 (Box 667)
  - Grasso, Doctor, 1979 (Box 667)
  - Grasso, Doctor, 1977-1978 (Box 667)
  - Grasso, Susane, 1977 (Box 667)
  - Gridiron Dinner, Washington D.C., 1975 March 22 (Box 667)
  - Hartley, 1978 (Box 667)
  - Health, 1979 (Box 667)
  - Helicopter, 1978 (Box 667)
  - Highway Safety, 1978 (Box 667)
  - Hold (B), 1977-1978 (Box 667)
  - Honorariums (B), 1978 (Box 667)
  - Honorary Chairperson (B), 1977-1978 (Box 667)
  - Honorary Chairperson (B), 1979 (Box 667)
  - Honorary Membership (B), 1975 (Box 668)
  - Honorary Membership (B), 1976 (Box 668)
  - Honorary Membership (B), 1978 (Box 668)
  - Honorary Membership (B), 1979 (Box 668)
  - Housing (I), 1979 (Box 668)
  - HUD/Meeting With Secretary Harris, 1978-1979 (Box 668)
  - Hudak, Eva (B), 1979 (Box 668)
  - [Inaugural - Invitations Lists], 1979 (Box 668)
  - Inauguration, 1975 January 8 (Box 668)
  - [International Women’s Year] - IWY, 1979 (Box 668)
  - [Invitations] (B), 1978 - 1979 (Box 668)
  - [Invitations/Replies] (Box 668)
  - [Invitations], 1978 January 1-March 26 (Box 669)
  - [Invitations], 1978 March 27-May 28 (Box 670)
  - [Invitations], 1978 May 29-August 13 (Box 671)
  - [Invitations], 1978 August 14-October 22 (Box 672)
  - [Invitations], 1978 October 23-December 31 (Folder 673)
  - Invitations Received (I), 1981 (Box 673)
  - Iranian Situation, 1979 (Box 673)
  - Italian Family File, 1976-1978 (Box 673)
  - Italian Historical Society, 1976-1977 (Box 673)
  - Italian Papal Trip (O), 1978 October (Box 673)
  - Judicial, 1979 (Box 673)
  - Labor, 1979 (Box 673)
  - Lauralton Hall - Diamond Jubilee, 1980 (Box 673)
  - Legislation (B), 1977 (Box 673)
  - Legislation, 1979 (Box 673)
  - [Library and Information Services - Governor’s Conference], 1978 (Box 673)
  - Manchester Community College (B), 1979 (Box 673)
  - Mass Cards (B), 1978 (Box 673)
  - Mass Cards - Hospitalization, 1980 April (Box 673)
  - Mass, Gifts, Special Letters - Duplicate List (Box 673)
  - Masses - Thank You (B), 1978 (Box 674)
  - Meet the Press, 1975 (Box 674)
  - Memorandum File - Confidential, 1978 (Box 674)
  - Mental Health, 1979 (Box 674)
  - Mental Health/Blue Hills Hospital, 1979 (Box 674)
  - Mental Retardation, 1977 (Box 674)
  - Mental Retardation, 1979 (Box 674)
  - Military, 1979 (Box 674)
  - Miscellaneous (B), 1978 (Box 674)
  - [Miscellaneous], 1976-1977 (Box 674)
  - [Miscellaneous - Book and Pamphlets], 1979-1980 (Box 674)
  - [Miscellaneous Letters] (B), 1975-1976 (Box 674)
  - [Miscellaneous], 1979-1980 (Box 674)
  - Miscellaneous [Letters] (B), 1979-1980 (Box 675)
  - National Governor’s Association, 1977-1978 (Box 675)
  - New London Drop-in Learning Center, 1978-1979 (Box 675)
  - News clippings and Photos (B), 1974-1977 (Box 675)
  - Norwich Office (B), 1975 (Box 675)
  - Office of Administrative Services, 1977-1978 (Box 675)
  - [Office of Policy and Management] OPM, 1979 (Box 675)
  - Open - Sometime (B), 1975-1976 (Box 676)
  - Paid Speeches, 1975-1976 (Box 676)
  - Painter - Governor’s Portrait - Mrs. Patricelli (B), 1976 (Box 676)
  - Personal (B), 1974-1975 (Box 676)
  - Personal (B), 1978-1980 (Box 676)
  - [Personal II] (B), 1980 (Box 677)
  - [Personal III] (B), 1979-1981 (Box 677)
  - Personnel (B), 1978 (Box 677)
  - Personnel, 1979 (Box 677)
  - Photos (B), 1979-1980 (Box 678)
  - [Photos - ETG - Education & Research Systems], 1980 (Box 678)
  - [Photos of the Governor] (Box 678)
  - Photographs (B), 1978 (Box 678)
  - [Photographs - Album of the American Family], 1980 (Box 678)
  - [Photographs - Hedges], 1981 (Box 678)
  - Portrait (I), 1979 (Box 678)
  - [President Carter/Camp David], 1979 (Box 678)
  - Press Releases, 1981 (Box 678)
  - Public Safety, 1979 (Box 679)
  - Public Safety Commissioner - TX’s for Recommendations - (O) (Box 679)
  - 1979 January 10 (Box 679)
  - PUCA, 1979 (Box 679)
  - [Rao, P.J. Jr. - “The Rock, the Torch and the Gavel”], 1978 (Box 679)
  - Recommendations (B), 1978 (Box 679)
  - Recommendations Denied (B), 1979 (Box 679)
  - Recommendations from Governor, 1979 (Box 679)
  - Recommendations to Governor, 1979 (Box 679)
  - Registrar of Voters List, 1974 (Box 679)
  - Requests, 1979 (Box 679)
  - [Requests], 1981 (Box 679)
  - Requests for Governor Pix & Eulogy, 1981 (Box 679)
  - Residence, 1979 (Box 679)
  - Residence File, 1978 (Box 679)
  - Resignation, 1978-1979 (Box 679)
  - Resolutions, 1980-1981 (Box 679)
  - Resolutions in Honor of Governor Ella Grasso, 1980-1981 (Box 679)
  - Resume, 1979 (Box 679)
  - [Revenue Services], 1979 (Box 679)
  - [Saint Patrick's Day], 1980 (Box 679)
  - Salt II Conference, 1978 December 5 (Box 679)
  - Saturn Phot., 1980 (Box 679)
  - Schedules (Box 679)
    - Weekend, 1975 (Box 680)
    - [Miscellaneous], 1975 (Box 680)
    - 1976 January-June (Box 680)
    - 1976 July-1977 December (Box 681)
    - 19778-1979 (Box 682)
    - 1980 (Box 683)
  - Seasons Passes (B), 1979 (Box 683)
  - Secretary of State, 1979 (Box 683)
  - [Sendzimir, Inc.], 1980 (Box 683)
  - Silver Bowl Log and Letters (I), 1976-1977 (Box 683)
  - Social Services (B), 1978 (Box 683)
  - Social Services, 1979 (Box 683)
  - Solicitations (I), 1978 (Box 683)
  - Solicitations (I), 1980 (Box 683)
  - [Southern Office - David Mack], 1979 (Box 683)
  - [Special Olympics], 1979 (Box 683)
  - Special Revenue (Box 683)
  - Speech Fees, 1975-1978 (Box 684)
  - Speed List, 1975-1976 (Box 684)
  - Stanford Office, 1975 (Box 684)
  - State Convention Delegates, 1978 (Box 684)
  - [Stonington - Development Grant], 1980 (Box 684)
  - Subscriptions, 1974-1978 (Box 684)
  - Support (B), 1979 (Box 684)
  - [Tape Recording - Misc.] (Box 684)
  - Tax, 1979 (Box 684)
  - [Technical Papers - Sheridan/Kelly] (Box 684)
  - [Thank Yous] (Box 684)
    - A (O), 1977-1979 (Box 684)
    - Ba-Bl (O), 1977-1979 (Box 684)
    - Bo-Bz (O), 1977-1979 (Box 684)
    - Ca-Ci (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - Cl-Cz (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - D (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - E (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - F (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - G (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - H (O), 1977-1979 (Box 685)
    - I (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - J (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - K (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - Ma-Me (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - Mac-Mc (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - Mi-Mz (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - N (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - O (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - P (O), 1977-1979 (Box 686)
    - Q (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - R (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - Sa-Sh (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - Si-Sz (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - T (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - U (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - V (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - W (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - X (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - Y (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - Z (O), 1977-1979 (Box 687)
    - [G-P] (O), 1980-1981 (Box 688)
    - [R-Z] (O), 1980-1981 (Box 688)
  - [Thank you - Birthdays] (B), 1979 (Box 688)
  - [Thank You - Birthdays] (B), 1979 (Box 689)
  - Thank You - Canate - Mag. Letter (B), 1978 (Box 689)
  - [Thank You], 1978 December (Box 689)
  - Thank You Gift (Box 689)
  - Thank You - (General) (B), 1979-1980 (Box 690)
  - [Thank You - Invitations Refused] (B), 1980 (Box 690)
  - Thank You Letters (I), 1978-1980 (Box 690)
  - [Thank You Letters]: (Box 691)
    - A-C (O), 1979-1980 (Box 691)
    - D-H (O), 1979-1980 (Box 691)
    - I-M (O), 1979-1980 (Box 691)
    - N-S (O), 1979-1980 (Box 691)
    - T-Z (O), 1979-1980 (Box 691)
  - [Thank You - Memorials] (B), 1981 (Box 691)
  - Thank You - Miscellaneous] (B), 1976 (Box 691)
  - [Thank You - Miscellaneous] (B), 1978 (Box 692)
  - [Thanks to Ching Delegation] (Box 692)
  - Transportation, Department of, 1977-1978 (Box 692)
  - [Transportation], Dot, 1979 (Box 692)
  - Travel, 1975 (Box 692)
  - Treasurer, 1976-1979 (Box 692)
  - Tufts School, 1979 (Box 692)
  - TX’s to ETG (B), 1979-1980 (Box 692)
  - United States Reps and Senators, 1977 (Box 692)
  - UCONN, 1978-1979 (Box 692)
  - UCONN/Fine Arts Facility Ground Breaking, 1978 (Box 692)
  - UCONN Newspaper, 1980 (Box 692)
  - Western Conn. State College, 1979 (Box 692)
  - WCSC Campus - Information, 1979 (Box 692)
  - White House Info and Correspondence (B), 1976-1978 (Box 692)
  - Women, 1979 (Box 692)
  - Women’s Political Caucus, 1975 (Box 692)
  - Yale - New Haven Hospital, 1979 (Box 692)
- Part VI Subject Files, 1979-1981
  There are no boxes 701-730.
  - Acknowledgements, 1980 (Box 693)
  - Aging, 1980 (Box 693)
  - Aging - Nursing Home Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 693)
  - Appointments, 1980 (Box 693)
  - Arts, 1980 (Box 693)
  - Auditors, 1980 (Box 693)
  - Banking, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Children, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Children - memos to & from Commissioner Marcus, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Civil Preparedness, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Civil Preparedness - memos to & from Director Mancuso, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Combined Health Appeal, 1980 (Box 694)
  - Commissioners Biweekly Reports (Box 694)
    - 1979 March 9-August 7 (Box 694)
    - 1979 August 14-1980 May 7 (Box 695)
    - 1980 May 8-December 16 (Box 696)
  - Comptroller - memos to & from Caldwell, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Corrections, K-T, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Corrections, A-Z, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Council of State Governments, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Eastern Office, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Economic Development, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Economic Development - Taiwan, 1980 (Box 697)
  - Education, A-Z, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Education - Aid to Disadvantaged Children, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Education 0- Higher Education, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Education - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Education - UConn, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Education - Vocational, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Elections Commission, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Environmental Protection, A-Z, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Environmental Protection - Long Island Sound, 1975 (Box 698)
  - Environmental Protection - Silver Sands, 1979 (Box 698)
  - Filer Committee, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Handicapped, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Health, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Health - memos to & from Douglas Lloyd, 1980 (Box 698)
  - Housing, 1980 (Box 699)
  - Human Resources, 1980 (Box 699)
  - [Human Resources - memos to & from Commissioner] Manning, 1980 (Box 699)
  - Income Maintenance, 9180 (Box 699)
  - Legis[lation], 1980 (Box 699)
  - Mental Health, 1980 (Box 699)
  - Mental R[etardation], 1980 (Box 699)
  - Misc[ellaneous], 1980 (Box 699)
  - OPM [Office of Policy & Management[, 1979-1980 (Box 699)
  - OPM - Energy Conservation - Liquor Distributors, 1979-1980 (Box 699)
  - P[ublic] W[orks], 1980 (Box 699)
  - Resume, 1980 (Box 699)
  - Rev[enue] Ser[vices], 1980 (Box 699)
  - Sec[retary] of [the] St[ate], 1980 (Box 699)
  - Spangler, Jon Eric, 1980 (Box 699)
  - DOT, 1980 (Box 699)
  - [DOT - memos to & from Commissioner] Powers, 1980 (Box 700)
  - [Lauralton Hall - Diamond Jubilee], 1981 (Box 731)
  - [Photo - ETG - Education & Research Systems], 1979 (Box 731)
  - [Saturn Photo], 1980 (Box 731)
- Part VII Supplementary Files, 1971-1980
  - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1974 (Box 732)
  - Candidacy Announced, 1974 January 19 (Box 732)
  - News Releases - Index (Box 732)
  - [News Releases: #1 through #124] (Box 732)
  - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1974 (Box 733)
  - [News Releases: #125 through #185] (Box 733)
  - Index of Speeches (Box 733)
  - [Speeches #1 through #39] (Box 733)
  - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1974 (Box 734)
  - [Speeches #40 through #53] (Box 734)
  - [Other news releases, statements, etc..] (Box 734)
    - Public Transportation (5-3) (Box 734)
    - Utilities, 25 issues for and against (5/20) (Box 734)
    - Statement at Vallee's Dinner (5/20) (Box 734)
    - Why I Should be Nominated for Governor (7/11) (Box 734)
    - Oil Refineries (7/22) (Box 734)
    - Statement in Democratic Newsletter (Box 734)
    - Cyprus (8/30) (Box 734)
    - Income Tax (9/6) (Box 734)
    - Ford’s Pardon, Nixon (9/8) (Box 734)
    - 5th Democratic Primary Results (9/10) (Box 734)
    - Super Pricing (Elderly) Norwich (9/12) (Box 734)
    - Caldwell Hits Ford on Economy (9/19) (Box 734)
    - Key Issues - Pitney Bowes (9/25) (Box 734)
    - Key Issues - GE (9/25) (Box 734)
    - Release for Reps/Sens Housing (10/14) (Box 734)
    - Files Injunction (10/16) (Box 734)
    - PUC Injunction Writ (10/17) (Box 734)
    - For Waterbury Republican (10/24) (Box 734)
    - Super pricing, Stratford (10/25) (Box 734)
    - Letters, DTC/high school (10/25) (Box 734)
    - Proposed Release (10/29) (Box 734)
    - Bailey Chides Laudone (10/30) (Box 734)
    - Bills (Box 734)
  - [Notebook - Copies of Newspaper Campaign Stories] (Box 734)
  - Gubernatorial Campaign, 1974 (Box 735)
  - Ella - New Releases Washington (Box 735)
  - Congressional Press Releases (Box 735)
  - Notebook: Member’s Personal Voting Records - 92D Congress, 1971-1972 (Box 735)
    - Ella T. Grasso (Box 735)
  - Notebook: Member’s personal Voting Records 93D Congress, 1973-1974 (Box 735)
    - Ella T. Grasso (Box 735)
  - Legislative Matter (Box 736)
    - [Blue Laws] (B) (Box 736)
    - 1978 May (Box 736)
    - [Collective Bargaining] (Box 736)
    - 1978 May (B) (Box 736)
    - [Correspondence] (Box 736)
    - 1977 January (B) (Box 736)
    - 1977 February 1 - 14 (I) (Box 736)
    - 1977 February 15-28 (B) (Box 736)
    - 1977 March 1-20 (I) (Box 737)
    - 1977 March 20-30 (B) (Box 737)
    - 1977 April 1-10 (B) (Box 737)
    - 1977 April 11/19 (I) (Box 737)
    - 1977 April 20/25 (I) (Box 737)
    - 1977 April 26-30 (B) (Box 738)
    - 1977 May 1/15 (I) (Box 738)
    - 1977 May 16-31 (I) (Box 739)
    - 1977 June 1-15 (I) (Box 739)
    - 1977 June 15-30 (B) (Box 739)
    - 1977 July 1-15 (B) (Box 739)
    - 1977 June - 1978 May (I) (Box 739)
    - 1979 (Box 740)
    - [Gay Rights Bill] (Box 740)
    - 1977 (Box 740)
    - [Labor Legislation] (Box 740)
    - 1977 (Box 740)
    - [Legislative Acts Signed] (Box 740)
    - 1978 March 2, March 7, March 20, March 22 (Box 740)
    - 1978 March 29, March 31, April 4 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 11, April 12, April 13, January 14 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 19 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 20 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 25 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 26 (Box 740)
    - 1978 April 27 (Box 740)
    - 1978 May 1, May 2, May 3 (Box 740)
    - 1978 May 4 (Box 740)
    - 1978 May 10 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 17 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 18 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 23 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 24 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 25 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 26 (Box 741)
    - 1978 May 29, May 30 (Box 741)
    - 1978 June 1 (Box 742)
    - 1978 June 1 (Box 742)
    - 1978 June 2 (Box 742)
    - 1978 June 6 (Box 742)
    - 1978 June 7 (Box 742)
    - 1978 June 8 (Box 743)
    - 1979 March 5 (Box 743)
    - 1979 March 7 (Box 743)
    - 1979 March 29 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 3 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 17 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 18 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 23 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 26 (Box 743)
    - 1979 April 30 (Box 743)
    - 1979 May 2 (Box 743)
    - 1979 May 3 (Box 743)
    - 1979 May 7 (Box 743)
    - 1979 May 8 (Box 743)
    - 1979 May 9 (Box 743)